{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.trc:syl.2ch..2ch..1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549119479611","data":{"timestamp":" 1549119479611"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" e3cf5f8b-9556-45dd-9181-7235902e6080"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.trc_syl.2ch..2ch..1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_su"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.trc:syl.2ch..2ch..1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549119482469","data":{"timestamp":" 1549119482468"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" e3cf5f8b-9556-45dd-9181-7235902e6080"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.trc_syl.2ch..2ch..1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_su"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.trc:syl.2ch..2ch..1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549119490709","data":{"timestamp":" 1549119490708"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" e3cf5f8b-9556-45dd-9181-7235902e6080"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.trc_syl.2ch..2ch..1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_vi"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" v"," userResponse":" v"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.trc:syl.2ch..2ch..1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549119493074","data":{"timestamp":" 1549119493074"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" e3cf5f8b-9556-45dd-9181-7235902e6080"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.trc_syl.2ch..2ch..1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_vi"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.trc:syl.2ch..2ch..1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549119502412","data":{"timestamp":" 1549119502411"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" e3cf5f8b-9556-45dd-9181-7235902e6080"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.trc_syl.2ch..2ch..1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ve"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" v"," userResponse":" v"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.trc:syl.2ch..2ch..1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549119504846","data":{"timestamp":" 1549119504846"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" e3cf5f8b-9556-45dd-9181-7235902e6080"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.trc_syl.2ch..2ch..1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ve"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.trc:syl.2ch..2ch..1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549119516345","data":{"timestamp":" 1549119516345"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" e3cf5f8b-9556-45dd-9181-7235902e6080"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.trc_syl.2ch..2ch..1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mi"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.trc:syl.2ch..2ch..1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549119518936","data":{"timestamp":" 1549119518936"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" e3cf5f8b-9556-45dd-9181-7235902e6080"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.trc_syl.2ch..2ch..1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mi"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.trc:syl.2ch..2ch..1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549119529821","data":{"timestamp":" 1549119529821"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" e3cf5f8b-9556-45dd-9181-7235902e6080"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.trc_syl.2ch..2ch..1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ya"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.trc:syl.2ch..2ch..1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549119533144","data":{"timestamp":" 1549119533143"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" e3cf5f8b-9556-45dd-9181-7235902e6080"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.trc_syl.2ch..2ch..1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ya"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.trc:syl.2ch..2ch..1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549119542787","data":{"timestamp":" 1549119542787"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" e3cf5f8b-9556-45dd-9181-7235902e6080"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.trc_syl.2ch..2ch..1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_jo"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.trc:syl.2ch..2ch..1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549119545192","data":{"timestamp":" 1549119545192"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" e3cf5f8b-9556-45dd-9181-7235902e6080"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.trc_syl.2ch..2ch..1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_jo"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.trc:syl.2ch..2ch..1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549119558846","data":{"timestamp":" 1549119558846"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" e3cf5f8b-9556-45dd-9181-7235902e6080"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.trc_syl.2ch..2ch..1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mu"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.trc:syl.2ch..2ch..1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549119561195","data":{"timestamp":" 1549119561195"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" e3cf5f8b-9556-45dd-9181-7235902e6080"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.trc_syl.2ch..2ch..1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mu"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.trc:syl.2ch..2ch..1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549119570253","data":{"timestamp":" 1549119570253"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" e3cf5f8b-9556-45dd-9181-7235902e6080"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.trc_syl.2ch..2ch..1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_yu"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.trc:syl.2ch..2ch..1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549119573529","data":{"timestamp":" 1549119573529"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" e3cf5f8b-9556-45dd-9181-7235902e6080"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.trc_syl.2ch..2ch..1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_yu"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.trc:syl.2ch..2ch..1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549119581869","data":{"timestamp":" 1549119581869"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" e3cf5f8b-9556-45dd-9181-7235902e6080"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.trc_syl.2ch..2ch..1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mo"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.trc:syl.2ch..2ch..1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549119583393","data":{"timestamp":" 1549119583393"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" e3cf5f8b-9556-45dd-9181-7235902e6080"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.trc_syl.2ch..2ch..1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mo"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.trc:syl.2ch..2ch..1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549119593568","data":{"timestamp":" 1549119593568"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" e3cf5f8b-9556-45dd-9181-7235902e6080"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.trc_syl.2ch..2ch..1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_fe"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.trc:syl.2ch..2ch..1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549119594598","data":{"timestamp":" 1549119594598"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" e3cf5f8b-9556-45dd-9181-7235902e6080"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.trc_syl.2ch..2ch..1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_fe"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.trc:syl.2ch..2ch..1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549119603716","data":{"timestamp":" 1549119603716"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" e3cf5f8b-9556-45dd-9181-7235902e6080"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.trc_syl.2ch..2ch..1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_fe"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.trc:syl.2ch..2ch..1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549119617680","data":{"timestamp":" 1549119617680"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 32a343e4-36a9-4575-bcc7-444b8486771d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.trc_syl.2ch..2ch..1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_saba"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.trc:syl.2ch..2ch..1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549119618433","data":{"timestamp":" 1549119618433"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 32a343e4-36a9-4575-bcc7-444b8486771d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.trc_syl.2ch..2ch..1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_saba"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" q"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.trc:syl.2ch..2ch..1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549119619324","data":{"timestamp":" 1549119619323"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 32a343e4-36a9-4575-bcc7-444b8486771d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.trc_syl.2ch..2ch..1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_saba"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.trc:syl.2ch..2ch..1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549119620433","data":{"timestamp":" 1549119620433"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 32a343e4-36a9-4575-bcc7-444b8486771d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.trc_syl.2ch..2ch..1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_saba"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.trc:syl.2ch..2ch..1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549119634510","data":{"timestamp":" 1549119634510"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 32a343e4-36a9-4575-bcc7-444b8486771d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.trc_syl.2ch..2ch..1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_su"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.trc:syl.2ch..2ch..1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549119638384","data":{"timestamp":" 1549119638384"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 32a343e4-36a9-4575-bcc7-444b8486771d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.trc_syl.2ch..2ch..1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_su"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.trc:syl.2ch..2ch..1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549119645920","data":{"timestamp":" 1549119645920"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 32a343e4-36a9-4575-bcc7-444b8486771d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.trc_syl.2ch..2ch..1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_vi"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.trc:syl.2ch..2ch..1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549119647387","data":{"timestamp":" 1549119647387"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 32a343e4-36a9-4575-bcc7-444b8486771d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.trc_syl.2ch..2ch..1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_vi"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" v"," userResponse":" v"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.trc:syl.2ch..2ch..1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549119658969","data":{"timestamp":" 1549119658969"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 32a343e4-36a9-4575-bcc7-444b8486771d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.trc_syl.2ch..2ch..1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ve"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.trc:syl.2ch..2ch..1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549119660124","data":{"timestamp":" 1549119660124"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 32a343e4-36a9-4575-bcc7-444b8486771d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.trc_syl.2ch..2ch..1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ve"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" v"," userResponse":" v"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.trc:syl.2ch..2ch..1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549119667443","data":{"timestamp":" 1549119667443"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 32a343e4-36a9-4575-bcc7-444b8486771d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.trc_syl.2ch..2ch..1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mi"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.trc:syl.2ch..2ch..1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549119668645","data":{"timestamp":" 1549119668645"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 32a343e4-36a9-4575-bcc7-444b8486771d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.trc_syl.2ch..2ch..1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mi"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.trc:syl.2ch..2ch..1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549119673624","data":{"timestamp":" 1549119673623"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 32a343e4-36a9-4575-bcc7-444b8486771d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.trc_syl.2ch..2ch..1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_mi"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549119679471","data":{"timestamp":" 1549119679470"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 32a343e4-36a9-4575-bcc7-444b8486771d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.trc_syl.2ch..2ch..1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_mi"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:syl.2ch..2ch..2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549119686807","data":{"timestamp":" 1549119686807"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 32a343e4-36a9-4575-bcc7-444b8486771d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.trc_syl.2ch..2ch..1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_mi"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549119691930","data":{"timestamp":" 1549119691929"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 32a343e4-36a9-4575-bcc7-444b8486771d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.trc_syl.2ch..2ch..1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_mi"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.2ch..2ch.noShow..16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549119697413","data":{"timestamp":" 1549119697413"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 32a343e4-36a9-4575-bcc7-444b8486771d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.trc_syl.2ch..2ch..1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_mi"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549119701943","data":{"timestamp":" 1549119701943"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 32a343e4-36a9-4575-bcc7-444b8486771d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.trc_syl.2ch..2ch..1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_mi"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:syl.2ch..2ch..3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549119708861","data":{"timestamp":" 1549119708861"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 32a343e4-36a9-4575-bcc7-444b8486771d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.trc_syl.2ch..2ch..1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_mi"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:5..15.off1.3__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549119713855","data":{"timestamp":" 1549119713855"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 32a343e4-36a9-4575-bcc7-444b8486771d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.trc_syl.2ch..2ch..1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_mi"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.2ch..2ch.noShow..17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549119719184","data":{"timestamp":" 1549119719183"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 32a343e4-36a9-4575-bcc7-444b8486771d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.trc_syl.2ch..2ch..1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_mi"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549119723380","data":{"timestamp":" 1549119723380"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 32a343e4-36a9-4575-bcc7-444b8486771d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.trc_syl.2ch..2ch..1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_mi"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.2ch..2ch..4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549119731076","data":{"timestamp":" 1549119731076"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 32a343e4-36a9-4575-bcc7-444b8486771d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.trc_syl.2ch..2ch..1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_mi"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549119740849","data":{"timestamp":" 1549119740849"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 32a343e4-36a9-4575-bcc7-444b8486771d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.trc_syl.2ch..2ch..1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_mi"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.2ch..2ch..4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549119773034","data":{"timestamp":" 1549119773034"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 41eec81c-7e80-4f68-a771-d468d7d465ba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.2ch..2ch..4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_jo"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.2ch..2ch..4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549119774911","data":{"timestamp":" 1549119774911"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 41eec81c-7e80-4f68-a771-d468d7d465ba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.2ch..2ch..4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_jo"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.2ch..2ch..4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549119798201","data":{"timestamp":" 1549119798200"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 41eec81c-7e80-4f68-a771-d468d7d465ba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.2ch..2ch..4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_lo"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.2ch..2ch..4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549119800008","data":{"timestamp":" 1549119800008"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 41eec81c-7e80-4f68-a771-d468d7d465ba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.2ch..2ch..4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_lo"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.2ch..2ch..4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549119810464","data":{"timestamp":" 1549119810464"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 41eec81c-7e80-4f68-a771-d468d7d465ba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.2ch..2ch..4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_gu"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.2ch..2ch..4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549119814058","data":{"timestamp":" 1549119814058"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 41eec81c-7e80-4f68-a771-d468d7d465ba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.2ch..2ch..4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_gu"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.2ch..2ch..4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549119822473","data":{"timestamp":" 1549119822473"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 41eec81c-7e80-4f68-a771-d468d7d465ba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.2ch..2ch..4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_za"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" z"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.2ch..2ch..4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549119824219","data":{"timestamp":" 1549119824219"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 41eec81c-7e80-4f68-a771-d468d7d465ba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.2ch..2ch..4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_za"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.2ch..2ch..4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549119833316","data":{"timestamp":" 1549119833316"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 41eec81c-7e80-4f68-a771-d468d7d465ba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.2ch..2ch..4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mo"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.2ch..2ch..4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549119834911","data":{"timestamp":" 1549119834911"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 41eec81c-7e80-4f68-a771-d468d7d465ba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.2ch..2ch..4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mo"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.2ch..2ch..4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549119842687","data":{"timestamp":" 1549119842687"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 41eec81c-7e80-4f68-a771-d468d7d465ba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.2ch..2ch..4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_sa"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.2ch..2ch..4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549119844115","data":{"timestamp":" 1549119844115"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 41eec81c-7e80-4f68-a771-d468d7d465ba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.2ch..2ch..4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_sa"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.2ch..2ch..4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549119849849","data":{"timestamp":" 1549119849849"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 41eec81c-7e80-4f68-a771-d468d7d465ba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.2ch..2ch..4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_sa"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.2ch..2ch..4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549119880059","data":{"timestamp":" 1549119880059"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 41eec81c-7e80-4f68-a771-d468d7d465ba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.2ch..2ch..4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ne"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.2ch..2ch..4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549119882793","data":{"timestamp":" 1549119882793"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 41eec81c-7e80-4f68-a771-d468d7d465ba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.2ch..2ch..4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ne"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.2ch..2ch..4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549119899823","data":{"timestamp":" 1549119899823"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 41eec81c-7e80-4f68-a771-d468d7d465ba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.2ch..2ch..4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ju"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.2ch..2ch..4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549119901998","data":{"timestamp":" 1549119901998"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 41eec81c-7e80-4f68-a771-d468d7d465ba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.2ch..2ch..4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ju"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.2ch..2ch..4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549119912319","data":{"timestamp":" 1549119912319"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 41eec81c-7e80-4f68-a771-d468d7d465ba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.2ch..2ch..4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ki"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.2ch..2ch..4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549119915079","data":{"timestamp":" 1549119915079"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 41eec81c-7e80-4f68-a771-d468d7d465ba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.2ch..2ch..4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ki"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.2ch..2ch..4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549119925825","data":{"timestamp":" 1549119925825"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 41eec81c-7e80-4f68-a771-d468d7d465ba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.2ch..2ch..4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ja"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.2ch..2ch..4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549119928736","data":{"timestamp":" 1549119928736"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 41eec81c-7e80-4f68-a771-d468d7d465ba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.2ch..2ch..4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ja"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.2ch..2ch..4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549119937874","data":{"timestamp":" 1549119937874"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 41eec81c-7e80-4f68-a771-d468d7d465ba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.2ch..2ch..4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_ja"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549119951671","data":{"timestamp":" 1549119951671"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 41eec81c-7e80-4f68-a771-d468d7d465ba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.2ch..2ch..4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_ja"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549119961876","data":{"timestamp":" 1549119961875"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" a188525f-f47e-4d45-bc78-75208751e269"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ma_ku-ma-ra"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ma"," userResponse":" ma"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549119975852","data":{"timestamp":" 1549119975852"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" a188525f-f47e-4d45-bc78-75208751e269"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_pi_le-ta-pi"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pi"," userResponse":" le"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549119991373","data":{"timestamp":" 1549119991373"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" a188525f-f47e-4d45-bc78-75208751e269"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_pi_le-ta-pi"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pi"," userResponse":" ta"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549119996652","data":{"timestamp":" 1549119996652"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" a188525f-f47e-4d45-bc78-75208751e269"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_pi_le-ta-pi"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pi"," userResponse":" pi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549120001364","data":{"timestamp":" 1549120001364"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" a188525f-f47e-4d45-bc78-75208751e269"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ta_ze-vo-ta"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ta"," userResponse":" ta"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549120011288","data":{"timestamp":" 1549120011288"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" a188525f-f47e-4d45-bc78-75208751e269"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_pe_pe-ra-da"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pe"," userResponse":" pe"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549120015978","data":{"timestamp":" 1549120015978"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" a188525f-f47e-4d45-bc78-75208751e269"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ho_ye-ho-ra"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ho"," userResponse":" ho"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549120020664","data":{"timestamp":" 1549120020664"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" a188525f-f47e-4d45-bc78-75208751e269"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ju_ma-ju-na"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ju"," userResponse":" ju"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549120033330","data":{"timestamp":" 1549120033330"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" a188525f-f47e-4d45-bc78-75208751e269"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_wi_ge-wi-zo"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wi"," userResponse":" wi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549120038250","data":{"timestamp":" 1549120038250"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" a188525f-f47e-4d45-bc78-75208751e269"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_da_vo-go-da"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" da"," userResponse":" da"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549120043026","data":{"timestamp":" 1549120043025"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" a188525f-f47e-4d45-bc78-75208751e269"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ke_ke-si-ta"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ke"," userResponse":" ke"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549120048534","data":{"timestamp":" 1549120048534"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" a188525f-f47e-4d45-bc78-75208751e269"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ba_ku-ba-vu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ba"," userResponse":" ba"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549120054373","data":{"timestamp":" 1549120054370"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" a188525f-f47e-4d45-bc78-75208751e269"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_ba_ku-ba-vu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549120063976","data":{"timestamp":" 1549120063976"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 06449359-ac53-482e-895b-f25c9ba905ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_0-1-11"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549120069258","data":{"timestamp":" 1549120069258"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 06449359-ac53-482e-895b-f25c9ba905ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_13-4-5"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549120075045","data":{"timestamp":" 1549120075045"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 06449359-ac53-482e-895b-f25c9ba905ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_8-10-5"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549120092723","data":{"timestamp":" 1549120092723"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 06449359-ac53-482e-895b-f25c9ba905ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_9-3-12"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549120099281","data":{"timestamp":" 1549120099280"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 06449359-ac53-482e-895b-f25c9ba905ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_9-11-4"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549120103655","data":{"timestamp":" 1549120103655"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 06449359-ac53-482e-895b-f25c9ba905ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_0-1-5"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549120108284","data":{"timestamp":" 1549120108284"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 06449359-ac53-482e-895b-f25c9ba905ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_9-10-4"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549120113009","data":{"timestamp":" 1549120113009"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 06449359-ac53-482e-895b-f25c9ba905ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_9-11-7"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549120117271","data":{"timestamp":" 1549120117271"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 06449359-ac53-482e-895b-f25c9ba905ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_8-1-11"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549120121975","data":{"timestamp":" 1549120121974"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 06449359-ac53-482e-895b-f25c9ba905ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_1-3-5"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549120128718","data":{"timestamp":" 1549120128718"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 06449359-ac53-482e-895b-f25c9ba905ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_1-3-5"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549120135323","data":{"timestamp":" 1549120135323"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 06449359-ac53-482e-895b-f25c9ba905ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_1_1-3-5"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:cha..cha.syl.rand.all.stat.show.51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549120144621","data":{"timestamp":" 1549120144621"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 629d405c-3dee-48b5-8f9e-25a3cd7a6651"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_cha..cha.syl.rand.all.stat.show.51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_cha_je-cha-ng'e"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" cha"," userResponse":" cha"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:cha..cha.syl.rand.all.stat.show.51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549120149213","data":{"timestamp":" 1549120149213"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 629d405c-3dee-48b5-8f9e-25a3cd7a6651"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_cha..cha.syl.rand.all.stat.show.51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_cha_zi-vyu-cha"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" cha"," userResponse":" cha"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:cha..cha.syl.rand.all.stat.show.51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549120153861","data":{"timestamp":" 1549120153861"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 629d405c-3dee-48b5-8f9e-25a3cd7a6651"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_cha..cha.syl.rand.all.stat.show.51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_cha_mza-mmo-cha"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" cha"," userResponse":" cha"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:cha..cha.syl.rand.all.stat.show.51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549120158337","data":{"timestamp":" 1549120158336"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 629d405c-3dee-48b5-8f9e-25a3cd7a6651"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_cha..cha.syl.rand.all.stat.show.51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_cha_cha-mlo-se"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" cha"," userResponse":" cha"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:cha..cha.syl.rand.all.stat.show.51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549120162850","data":{"timestamp":" 1549120162850"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 629d405c-3dee-48b5-8f9e-25a3cd7a6651"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_cha..cha.syl.rand.all.stat.show.51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_cha_bwe-ro-cha"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" cha"," userResponse":" cha"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:cha..cha.syl.rand.all.stat.show.51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549120167490","data":{"timestamp":" 1549120167490"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 629d405c-3dee-48b5-8f9e-25a3cd7a6651"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_cha..cha.syl.rand.all.stat.show.51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_cha_tu-zo-cha"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" cha"," userResponse":" cha"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:cha..cha.syl.rand.all.stat.show.51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549120171954","data":{"timestamp":" 1549120171953"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 629d405c-3dee-48b5-8f9e-25a3cd7a6651"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_cha..cha.syl.rand.all.stat.show.51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_cha_chu-cha-nda"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" cha"," userResponse":" chu"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:cha..cha.syl.rand.all.stat.show.51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549120177310","data":{"timestamp":" 1549120177310"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 629d405c-3dee-48b5-8f9e-25a3cd7a6651"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_cha..cha.syl.rand.all.stat.show.51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_cha_chu-cha-nda"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" cha"," userResponse":" cha"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:cha..cha.syl.rand.all.stat.show.51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549120181757","data":{"timestamp":" 1549120181757"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 629d405c-3dee-48b5-8f9e-25a3cd7a6651"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_cha..cha.syl.rand.all.stat.show.51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_cha_cha-nu-mle"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" cha"," userResponse":" cha"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:cha..cha.syl.rand.all.stat.show.51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549120186395","data":{"timestamp":" 1549120186395"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 629d405c-3dee-48b5-8f9e-25a3cd7a6651"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_cha..cha.syl.rand.all.stat.show.51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_cha_cha-shu-pa"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" cha"," userResponse":" cha"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:cha..cha.syl.rand.all.stat.show.51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549120192642","data":{"timestamp":" 1549120192642"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 629d405c-3dee-48b5-8f9e-25a3cd7a6651"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_cha..cha.syl.rand.all.stat.show.51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_cha_ndu-bu-cha"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" cha"," userResponse":" cha"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:cha..cha.syl.rand.all.stat.show.51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549120198418","data":{"timestamp":" 1549120198417"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 629d405c-3dee-48b5-8f9e-25a3cd7a6651"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_cha..cha.syl.rand.all.stat.show.51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_cha_ndu-bu-cha"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549120207421","data":{"timestamp":" 1549120207421"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 721acaee-02af-4e5c-b0d6-3d84f801dabe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549120207645","data":{"timestamp":" 1549120207644"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 721acaee-02af-4e5c-b0d6-3d84f801dabe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549120208607","data":{"timestamp":" 1549120208607"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 721acaee-02af-4e5c-b0d6-3d84f801dabe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549120209904","data":{"timestamp":" 1549120209903"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 721acaee-02af-4e5c-b0d6-3d84f801dabe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549120212793","data":{"timestamp":" 1549120212792"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 721acaee-02af-4e5c-b0d6-3d84f801dabe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549120213646","data":{"timestamp":" 1549120213645"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 721acaee-02af-4e5c-b0d6-3d84f801dabe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549120213973","data":{"timestamp":" 1549120213971"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 721acaee-02af-4e5c-b0d6-3d84f801dabe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549120215214","data":{"timestamp":" 1549120215214"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 721acaee-02af-4e5c-b0d6-3d84f801dabe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549120218781","data":{"timestamp":" 1549120218781"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 721acaee-02af-4e5c-b0d6-3d84f801dabe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549120219774","data":{"timestamp":" 1549120219774"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 721acaee-02af-4e5c-b0d6-3d84f801dabe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549120220030","data":{"timestamp":" 1549120220030"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 721acaee-02af-4e5c-b0d6-3d84f801dabe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549120220993","data":{"timestamp":" 1549120220993"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 721acaee-02af-4e5c-b0d6-3d84f801dabe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549120223862","data":{"timestamp":" 1549120223861"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 721acaee-02af-4e5c-b0d6-3d84f801dabe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549120224899","data":{"timestamp":" 1549120224899"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 721acaee-02af-4e5c-b0d6-3d84f801dabe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549120225381","data":{"timestamp":" 1549120225380"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 721acaee-02af-4e5c-b0d6-3d84f801dabe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549120229894","data":{"timestamp":" 1549120229894"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 721acaee-02af-4e5c-b0d6-3d84f801dabe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549120229976","data":{"timestamp":" 1549120229976"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 721acaee-02af-4e5c-b0d6-3d84f801dabe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.cha..chu.asc.lc.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549120240002","data":{"timestamp":" 1549120240002"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 30d176a9-113d-466c-9a21-a7199aba085a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.cha..chu.asc.lc.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" cha"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.cha..chu.asc.lc.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549120242804","data":{"timestamp":" 1549120242804"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 30d176a9-113d-466c-9a21-a7199aba085a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.cha..chu.asc.lc.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" cha"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.cha..chu.asc.lc.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549120244367","data":{"timestamp":" 1549120244367"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 30d176a9-113d-466c-9a21-a7199aba085a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.cha..chu.asc.lc.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" che"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHE"," userResponse":" CHE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.cha..chu.asc.lc.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549120247266","data":{"timestamp":" 1549120247266"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 30d176a9-113d-466c-9a21-a7199aba085a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.cha..chu.asc.lc.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" che"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.cha..chu.asc.lc.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549120248828","data":{"timestamp":" 1549120248827"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 30d176a9-113d-466c-9a21-a7199aba085a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.cha..chu.asc.lc.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHI"," userResponse":" CHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.cha..chu.asc.lc.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549120251715","data":{"timestamp":" 1549120251715"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 30d176a9-113d-466c-9a21-a7199aba085a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.cha..chu.asc.lc.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.cha..chu.asc.lc.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549120253276","data":{"timestamp":" 1549120253276"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 30d176a9-113d-466c-9a21-a7199aba085a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.cha..chu.asc.lc.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" cho"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHO"," userResponse":" CHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.cha..chu.asc.lc.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549120256043","data":{"timestamp":" 1549120256043"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 30d176a9-113d-466c-9a21-a7199aba085a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.cha..chu.asc.lc.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" cho"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.cha..chu.asc.lc.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549120257598","data":{"timestamp":" 1549120257598"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 30d176a9-113d-466c-9a21-a7199aba085a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.cha..chu.asc.lc.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHU"," userResponse":" CHU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.cha..chu.asc.lc.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549120260468","data":{"timestamp":" 1549120260467"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 30d176a9-113d-466c-9a21-a7199aba085a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.cha..chu.asc.lc.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.cha..chu.asc.lc.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549120262480","data":{"timestamp":" 1549120262480"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 30d176a9-113d-466c-9a21-a7199aba085a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.cha..chu.asc.lc.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" chu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549120262663","data":{"timestamp":" 1549120262663"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 30d176a9-113d-466c-9a21-a7199aba085a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.cha..chu.asc.lc.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549120272857","data":{"timestamp":" 1549120272857"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 30d176a9-113d-466c-9a21-a7199aba085a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.cha..chu.asc.lc.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" chu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.cha..chu.asc.lc.39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549120279546","data":{"timestamp":" 1549120279545"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 30d176a9-113d-466c-9a21-a7199aba085a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.cha..chu.asc.lc.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" chu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549120285994","data":{"timestamp":" 1549120285994"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 30d176a9-113d-466c-9a21-a7199aba085a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.cha..chu.asc.lc.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" chu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549120300586","data":{"timestamp":" 1549120300586"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 3b6fa82c-e38f-4220-a723-ba3a41560810"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mgu_nje-nja-mgu"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mgu"," userResponse":" mgu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549120305412","data":{"timestamp":" 1549120305412"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 3b6fa82c-e38f-4220-a723-ba3a41560810"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mta_nji-mno-mta"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mta"," userResponse":" mta"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549120310803","data":{"timestamp":" 1549120310803"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 3b6fa82c-e38f-4220-a723-ba3a41560810"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nja_mwo-vya-nja"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nja"," userResponse":" nja"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549120316502","data":{"timestamp":" 1549120316502"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 3b6fa82c-e38f-4220-a723-ba3a41560810"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mpi_mpi-bwa-cha"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mpi"," userResponse":" mpi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549120321055","data":{"timestamp":" 1549120321055"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 3b6fa82c-e38f-4220-a723-ba3a41560810"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ndu_ndu-chi-nyi"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ndu"," userResponse":" ndu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549120327710","data":{"timestamp":" 1549120327710"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 3b6fa82c-e38f-4220-a723-ba3a41560810"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_thi_njo-swa-thi"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" thi"," userResponse":" thi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549120332878","data":{"timestamp":" 1549120332877"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 3b6fa82c-e38f-4220-a723-ba3a41560810"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nji_bwa-nji-mfa"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nji"," userResponse":" nji"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549120338188","data":{"timestamp":" 1549120338188"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 3b6fa82c-e38f-4220-a723-ba3a41560810"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mzu_mme-dha-mzu"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mzu"," userResponse":" mzu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549120343544","data":{"timestamp":" 1549120343544"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 3b6fa82c-e38f-4220-a723-ba3a41560810"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mki_mgo-mke-mki"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mki"," userResponse":" mki"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549120348601","data":{"timestamp":" 1549120348600"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 3b6fa82c-e38f-4220-a723-ba3a41560810"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nde_kwa-mwi-nde"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nde"," userResponse":" nde"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549120354371","data":{"timestamp":" 1549120354371"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 3b6fa82c-e38f-4220-a723-ba3a41560810"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_nde_kwa-mwi-nde"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549120361142","data":{"timestamp":" 1549120361141"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 3b6fa82c-e38f-4220-a723-ba3a41560810"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_nde_kwa-mwi-nde"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.nye..nye.noShow..19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549120380892","data":{"timestamp":" 1549120380891"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" be6899cf-27ec-4770-9eb7-f6e8d8eadf06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.nye..nye.noShow..19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_shu_nye_mla"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.nye..nye.noShow..19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549120387577","data":{"timestamp":" 1549120387577"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" be6899cf-27ec-4770-9eb7-f6e8d8eadf06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.nye..nye.noShow..19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_nye_mke_ta"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.nye..nye.noShow..19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549120394245","data":{"timestamp":" 1549120394245"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" be6899cf-27ec-4770-9eb7-f6e8d8eadf06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.nye..nye.noShow..19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_mka_nye_pa"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.nye..nye.noShow..19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549120400938","data":{"timestamp":" 1549120400937"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" be6899cf-27ec-4770-9eb7-f6e8d8eadf06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.nye..nye.noShow..19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_twe_nye_mo"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.nye..nye.noShow..19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549120407586","data":{"timestamp":" 1549120407585"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" be6899cf-27ec-4770-9eb7-f6e8d8eadf06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.nye..nye.noShow..19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ye_nye_mbe"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.nye..nye.noShow..19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549120414266","data":{"timestamp":" 1549120414266"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" be6899cf-27ec-4770-9eb7-f6e8d8eadf06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.nye..nye.noShow..19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_kwe_nye_mto"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.nye..nye.noShow..19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549120420990","data":{"timestamp":" 1549120420990"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" be6899cf-27ec-4770-9eb7-f6e8d8eadf06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.nye..nye.noShow..19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_mu_nye_mgu"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.nye..nye.noShow..19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549120427703","data":{"timestamp":" 1549120427703"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" be6899cf-27ec-4770-9eb7-f6e8d8eadf06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.nye..nye.noShow..19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_za_nye_mchi"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.nye..nye.noShow..19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549120434370","data":{"timestamp":" 1549120434369"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" be6899cf-27ec-4770-9eb7-f6e8d8eadf06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.nye..nye.noShow..19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_mfu_nye_zo"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.nye..nye.noShow..19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549120441834","data":{"timestamp":" 1549120441831"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" be6899cf-27ec-4770-9eb7-f6e8d8eadf06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.nye..nye.noShow..19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_mfu_nye_zo"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.nye..nye.noShow..19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549120450836","data":{"timestamp":" 1549120450835"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" be6899cf-27ec-4770-9eb7-f6e8d8eadf06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.nye..nye.noShow..19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_mfu_nye_zo"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549120456954","data":{"timestamp":" 1549120456953"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" be6899cf-27ec-4770-9eb7-f6e8d8eadf06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.nye..nye.noShow..19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_mfu_nye_zo"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.nya..nyu.asc.lc.32__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549120468987","data":{"timestamp":" 1549120468987"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 28d62f7b-030e-4c1d-b57f-bb66c69d9154"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.nya..nyu.asc.lc.32__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nya"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYA"," userResponse":" NYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.nya..nyu.asc.lc.32__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549120471540","data":{"timestamp":" 1549120471540"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 28d62f7b-030e-4c1d-b57f-bb66c69d9154"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.nya..nyu.asc.lc.32__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nya"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.nya..nyu.asc.lc.32__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549120473100","data":{"timestamp":" 1549120473100"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 28d62f7b-030e-4c1d-b57f-bb66c69d9154"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.nya..nyu.asc.lc.32__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nye"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYE"," userResponse":" NYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.nya..nyu.asc.lc.32__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549120476109","data":{"timestamp":" 1549120476109"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 28d62f7b-030e-4c1d-b57f-bb66c69d9154"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.nya..nyu.asc.lc.32__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nye"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.nya..nyu.asc.lc.32__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549120477685","data":{"timestamp":" 1549120477685"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 28d62f7b-030e-4c1d-b57f-bb66c69d9154"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.nya..nyu.asc.lc.32__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nyo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYO"," userResponse":" NYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.nya..nyu.asc.lc.32__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549120480140","data":{"timestamp":" 1549120480139"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 28d62f7b-030e-4c1d-b57f-bb66c69d9154"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.nya..nyu.asc.lc.32__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nyo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYO"," userResponse":" NYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.nya..nyu.asc.lc.32__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549120483121","data":{"timestamp":" 1549120483121"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 28d62f7b-030e-4c1d-b57f-bb66c69d9154"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.nya..nyu.asc.lc.32__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nyu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYU"," userResponse":" NYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.nya..nyu.asc.lc.32__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549120485731","data":{"timestamp":" 1549120485731"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 28d62f7b-030e-4c1d-b57f-bb66c69d9154"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.nya..nyu.asc.lc.32__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nyu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.nya..nyu.asc.lc.32__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549120487748","data":{"timestamp":" 1549120487747"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 28d62f7b-030e-4c1d-b57f-bb66c69d9154"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.nya..nyu.asc.lc.32__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" nyu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549120487925","data":{"timestamp":" 1549120487925"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_175721"," gameId":" 28d62f7b-030e-4c1d-b57f-bb66c69d9154"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.nya..nyu.asc.lc.32__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nyu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}